줄리가 보고 싶어
Man, I sure miss Julie.
Spanish midgets.
스페인 난쟁이들이
레슬링을 한다?
Spanish midgets wrestling....
줄리!
줄리 생각 날 만하네
Julie!
Okay, I see how you got there.
전화는 받으라고 울리는 거야
You ever figure out
what that thing's for?
이제 전화도 가려서 받을래
I'm trying this screening thing.
허구한 날 집에서 전화나 받으면
백수인 줄 알 거 아냐
If I always answer the phone,
people will think I have no life.
역시 로드리고가 짱이야!
My God!
Rodrigo never gets pinned!
어떻게 하는지 알죠?
At the sound of the beep,
you know what to do.
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
혹시 거기 밥 있나요?
난 제이드인데
This is Jade.
아직 이 번호를 쓰는지 몰라도
당신이 그리워서요
I don 't know if you 're still
at this number, but I was thinking...
...about how great it was.
I know it's been three years...
3년이나 흘렀지만
다시 만날 수 있을까요?
...but I was hoping
we could hook up again.
전화 걸 용기가 안 나서...
I barely had the nerve
to make this call...
- 어떻게 했게요?
- 어떻게 했지?
-...so you know what I did?
-What?
술을 마셨어요
옷도 다 벗어버리고
I got a little drunk...
...and naked.
나 밥이야!
Bob here!
The One With Five Steaks and An Eggplant
그간 어떻게 지냈어?
So what have you been up to?
여전히 똑같죠 뭐
에어로빅 가르치고
Oh, you know, the usual.
Teaching aerobics...
...partying way too much.
친구들 만나서 놀고
And in case you wondered...
참, 아는지 모르겠지만
... those are my legs on
the new James Bond poster.
내 다리가 007 영화의
포스터에 나왔어요
Can you hold on?
I have another call.
잠시만, 딴 전화가 와서
- 나 사랑에 빠졌어
- 알아
-I love her!
-I know.
-I'm back.
-So are we gonna get together?
- 나야
- 만날 수 있을까요?
그럼!
Absolutely.
How about tomorrow afternoon?
내일 오후 어때?
샌츄럴퍼크 카페에서
5시에 만날까?
Do you know Central Perk?
Say, five-ish?
Great. I'll see you then.
- 알았어요, 그 때 봐요
- 그래
좋았어!
전화 달아 둔 보람이 있네!
Having a phone has finally paid off.
목소리엔 속을지 몰라도
You do a good Bob impression...
내일 만나면 이럴 거야
'밥이 아니잖아! '
... but when she
sees you tomorrow...
...she's gonna realize
you're not Bob.
밥은 안 나올 테니
I'm hoping that when
Bob doesn't show up...
옆자리에 앉아 있다가
위로를 해주는 거야
...she'll seek comfort in the arms of
the stranger at the next table.
세상에! 넌 진짜 나쁜 놈이야!
Oh, my God.
You are pure evil.
Okay, pure evil...
그래, 나쁘지
... horny and alone.
여자에 굶주리면 다 그래
I've done this.
나도 그렇다고
Yeah, everybody's here.
응, 다들 같이 있어
얘들아, 뉴멕시코에 있는
줄리에게 인사해
Hey, everybody!
Say hi to Julie in New Mexico!
- 안녕, 줄리
- 안녕!
'안녕, 줄리' 좋아하네
Hi, Julie.
로스 생일 준비에
총 62달러 들어갔어
While Ross is on the phone...
...everybody owes me
62 bucks for his birthday.
혹시 반올림한 거 아냐?
Is there any chance that
you're rounding up from...
...you know...
20달러에서?
...from like 20?
Hey, we got the gift,
the concert and the cake.
선물, 콘서트 입장권에
케이크까지 샀어
케이크도 꼭 사야 해?
Do we need a cake?
나도 좀 과하다고 생각했지만...
I know it's a little steep.
엄청 과하지
But it's Ross.
하지만 로스 생일이잖아
- 그래, 맞아
- 알았어
It's Ross.
됐지? 그럼 나중에 봐
난 중요한 일이 있어서
See you later.
I gotta go...
...do a thing!
Okay, sweetheart,
I'll call you later.
밤에 다시 전화할게
정말 나갈 작정이야?
You're not going
through with this, are you?
You know, I think I might just.
말이라고 하시나!
다들 저녁에 뭐 해?
What are you guys
doing for dinner tonight?
난 이제부터 로스 생일 때문에
돈을 아껴야 돼
Well, I gotta start
saving up for Ross' birthday.
집에서 찬밥이나 먹을래
I guess I'll just stay home
and eat dust bunnies.
Can you believe
how much this costs?
너무 많은 것 같아
이런 생각 안 드니?
Do you guys ever
get the feeling that...
챈들러하고 로스는
... Chandler and those guys...
...don't get that
we don't make that much money?
우리가 자기네들처럼
돈을 많이 버는 줄 알아
맞아!
They always say
let's go here, let's go there.
맨날 여기도 가자
저기도 가자
Like we can afford to go
here and there.
우리가 여기저기 다닐
돈이 어디 있다고?
Yes, and we always have to go to,
you know, someplace nice.
맞아, 거기다 꼭
비싼 데만 가더라
사실은... 생일이라고 꼭
이렇게 할 것까진 없어
And we can't say anything about it,
because this is a birthday thing...
...and it's "for Ross."
단지 로스니까...
For Ross.
- 로스 때문에
-로스!
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
왜?
주방에서 평소처럼
지지고 볶고 하고 있는데
I'm at work...
...just an ordinary day,
chop, chop, saute, saute.
Suddenly, Leon, the manager,
calls me into his office.
지배인이 날 부르더니
점심 담당 주방장을 잘랐대!
They fired the lunch chef,
and guess who got the job?
후임이 누군지 알아?
그렇게 말해 놓고
네가 아니라면 끔찍한 일이지
If it's not you,
this is a horrible story.
Fortunately, it is me.
다행히 내가 됐어
게다가 내게 요리 재료
구매를 일임했어!
And they made me head of purchasing,
thank you!
정말 잘됐어!
That's so cool!
복도에서 챈들러하고
오빠도 봤는데
Anyway, I think we
should go out and celebrate.
근사한 곳에 가서
파티를 하자고
You know, someplace nice.
Someplace nice.
- 근사한 곳에서?
- 그렇대
How much you think
I can get for my kidney?
신장 팔면 얼마나 받을까?
너 그러면 못써
You can't do this.
구닥다리 방법으론 평생가도
저런 여자 못 만나!
I can't get a girl like that
with conventional methods.
지금 그게 문제냐?
저 여잔 밥에게 전화했어
It doesn't matter.
She wanted to call Bob. Bob could be
who she was meant to be with.
저 여자와 함께 있을
남자는 밥이라고
You may be destroying
their chance for happiness.
넌 잘될 수 있는 인연을
파괴하려는 중이고!
We don't know Bob.
우린 밥을 몰라
We know me. We like me.
Please let me be happy.
하지만 난 알잖아
나도 잘되게 놔둬!
여자에게 사실대로 말해
Go over there
and tell that woman the truth.
알았어
All right.
얼른!
Go.
안녕하세요?
네
고백할 게 있어서요
Listen, I have to....
I have to confess something.
뭐죠?
Yes?
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
어떤 바보가 당신을
바람맞혔을까?
- 어떻게 그걸...
- 모르겠어요!
-How did you
-I don't know.
이상한 느낌이 왔거든요
I just had this weird sense.
But that's me, I'm weird and sensitive.
난 이상하고 민감하죠
- 휴지 드려요?
- 고마워요
Tissue?
Thanks.
No, you keep the pack.
그냥 가지세요
전 오늘 다 울었거든요
I'm all cried out today.
다들 들어
'새 점심 주방장'에
임명된 내 동생의...
Here is to my sister,
the newly appointed head lunch chef.
Also in charge of purchasing.
요리 재료 구매 담당!
새 점심 주방장이며
구매 담당인...
Head lunch chef,
also in charge of purchasing
로랜드 책상도 쓰고!
Who has her own little desk
when Roland's not there.
Lunch chef, purchasing, own little desk
when Roland's not there...
점심 주방장, 구매 담당
로랜드 책상을 쓰는
-... here's to my
-Wait! And I got a beeper!
- 내 동생을 위하여...
-참, 삐삐도 생겼어!
죽인다!
- 구경 끝나면 알려 줘
- 미안해
That's fine, I'll just wait.
Sorry.
모니카를 위해!
Monica!
Are we ready to order?
주문하시겠어요?
- 아직 메뉴도 안 봤어요
- 보시고 부르세요
We haven't even looked yet.
When you do, let me know.
저기 의자 구석에
앉아 있을게요
I'll be over there
on the edge of my seat.
Look at these prices!
이렇게 비싸?
그래, 돌겠다니까
Yeah, these are pretty "cha-ching."
유명한 닭들을 쓰나?
I know! What are these,
famous chickens?
늦어서 미안해
승진 축하해, 모니카
Sorry I'm late.
Congratulations, Mon.
제이드와 황금의 오후를
보내고 왔단 말이지!
I'm not sorry I'm late.
How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
응답기에 재밌었다고
메시지를 남겨놨더군
Pretty incredible, according to
the message on my machine.
Why is this woman leaving a message
for you on my machine?
한데 왜 내 응답기에
메시지를 남겼지?
I told her that
my number was yours...
네 전화번호를 알려 줬거든
내 거 말하면 안 되잖아
... because I couldn't
tell her it was mine...
제이드는 내 전화번호가
밥 번호라고 생각하니까
... because she thinks
my number is Bob's number.
로퍼 아저씨가 전화하면
뭐라고 할까?
Tell me again.
What do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
Do I dare ask?
주문해도 될까요?
I'll start with the carpaccio,
and then the grilled prawns.
카르파초하고
석쇠에 구운 새우요리요
Great, same for me.
그거 괜찮겠네
저도 같은 거요
손님은?
And for the gentleman?
태국식 치킨 피자요
I'll have the Thai chicken pizza.
But if I get it without
the nuts and leeks and stuff...
땅콩하고 리크를 빼면
좀 깎아 주나요?
...is it cheaper?
You'd think, wouldn't you?
그럼 좋으시겠죠?
숙녀 분은?
사이드 샐러드
I will have the side salad.
무슨 음식의 사이드 말이죠?
And what would that
be on the side of?
글쎄요...
물과 함께 주세요
I don't know.
Just put it right here
next to my water.
손님께선?
And for you?
I'm gonna have a cup
of the cucumber soup and...
오이 수프하고...
수고하세요
...take care.
전 케이준 메기 요리요
I will have the Cajun catfish.
다른 것은?
Anything else?
Yes, how about a verse of
"Killing Me Softly"?
'Killing Me Softly'의
가사도 부탁해요
내 요리에다가
재채기 할 거죠?
You're gonna sneeze
in my fish, aren't you?
팁까지 포함해서
6으로 나누면...
Plus tip, divided by six....
일인당 28달러야
Everyone owes 28 bucks.
Everyone?
모두?
참, 미안해
Oh! You're right, I'm sorry.
고마워
Thank you.
모니카를 위한 자리인데
돈을 내게 할 순 없지
It's Monica's big night.
She shouldn't pay.
5로 다시 나누면...
So five of us is...
1인당 33달러 50센트야
...33. 50 a piece.
아냐, 그런 게 어딨어?
No. No way.
Sorry, not gonna happen.
이런, 위기의 순간이다
감 잡았어
Prom night flashback.
Sorry, Monica.
I'm happy you got promoted...
네가 승진한 것은
축하하지만
오이 수프가 33달러야?
... but cold cucumber mush
for 30-something bucks?
No!
아냐!
레이철은 샐러드 먹고
조이는 피자 먹었잖아!
Rachel just had that little salad...
...and Joey with his teeny pizza!
진정해, 피비
각자 계산하면 되잖아
Okay, Pheebs.
How about we'll each
pay for what we had?
It's no big deal.
- 별것도 아닌 걸로
- 너한텐 그렇지
Not for you.
왜들 그래?
All right, what's going on?
I don't wanna get
into this right now.
지금 그런 얘기를 하면
분위기만 나빠지잖아
It'll make everybody uncomfortable.
알았어
- 뭔데?
- 어서 말해 봐
You can tell us.
우리 사이에
못할 말이 어딨다고
Yeah, hello? It's us.
We'll be fine.
좋아
우리 셋 생각에는...
We three...
...feel like that...
때론 너희들이...
...sometimes you guys don't get that....
우린 너희들처럼
돈이 많지가 않아
We don't have
as much money as you.
그래
I hear you.
알았어
터놓고 얘기하자고
We can talk about that.
그럼...
Well, then...
얘기해 보자
...Iet's.
사실 돈을 문제 거리로
생각해 보지 않았어
I guess I just never think
of money as an issue.
-Because you have it.
-Good point!
- 넌 돈이 있으니까
- 좋은 지적이야
왜 진작 말 안 했지?
So how come you guys
haven't talked about this before?
항상 일이 생겼으니까
모니카 승진이나
Because it's always something.
Like with Monica's new job...
로스 생일 파티나...
...or the whole Ross' birthday hoopla.
잠깐만, 내 생일 때문에
부담주기는 싫은데...
I don't want my birthday to be
the source of any kind of negative....
파티 할 거야?
There's gonna be a hoopla?
그걸 하고 나면
그 다음엔 또...
Basically there's the thing,
and then the stuff after the thing
그럼 그건 그만두고
선물만 하면 되잖아
If it makes anybody feel better,
forget the thing...
...and we'll just do the gift.
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
그거라니?
선물 말고 또 있었어?
사실 '후티와 블로우피쉬'
콘서트에 가려고 했어
No, we were gonna go see
Hootie and the Blowfish.
Hootie and the
그게 정말...
난 라디오로 들으면 돼
I can catch them on the radio.
괜한 소리 마
콘서트에 가고 싶잖아
No. Now I feel bad.
You wanna go to the concert.
아냐, 내 생일인데
모두 함께 지내야지
No, look. It's my birthday...
...and the important thing
is that we're all together.
- 전부
- 함께
-All of us.
-Together.
콘서트엔 안 가도 돼
Not at the concert.
- 좋아
- 고마워
Thank you.
에볼라 바이러스 말인데
정말 무섭지?
So, the Ebola virus.
That's gotta suck, huh?
모니카, 가방에 뭐 들었니?
Gee, Monica.
What's in the bag?
나도 모르겠는데
뭐가 들었나 살펴볼까?
I don't know, Chandler.
Let's take a look.
무슨 학예회 하니?
Oh, it's like a skit.
6인분 저녁식사야!
Why, it's dinner for six.
Five steaks...
스테이크 다섯 개와
피비를 위한 가지!
...and an eggplant for Phoebe.
거래처를 바꾸었더니
감사의 표시로 주더라
We switched suppliers at work, and
they gave me the steaks as a thank-you.
잠깐, 아직 남았어
챈들러, 봉투에 뭐 들었지?
But wait, there's more.
Chandler, what is in that envelope?
By the way, this didn't
seem so dorky out in the hall.
복도에서 연습할 때는
이렇게 느끼하지 않았는데
그만 해!
'후티와 블로우피쉬' 콘서트
입장권 6장!
Why, it's six tickets to
Hootie and the Blowfish!
블로우피쉬!
The Blowfish!
돈은 우리가 낼 테니까
걱정하지 마
It's on us. So don't worry.
This is...
...our treat.
그래, 고마워
Thank you.
왜 다들 죽을상이야?
Could you be less enthused?
성의는 고맙지만
뭐랄까...
Look, it's a nice gesture. It is.
But it just feels like....
어떤데?
Like?
Charity.
적선 같아
Charity?
- 적선?
- 기분 풀자는 뜻이었어
We're just trying
to do a nice thing here.
But you have to understand, your
"nice thing" makes us feel about this big.
네 성의가 우릴
요만하게 느껴지게 해
아냐, 요만하게야
Actually, it makes us feel that big.
이해가 안 되는군
그럼 방법이 없잖아
I don't understand.
We can't win with you guys.
너희들의 그런 느낌이
우리 잘못은 아니잖아
If you guys feel this big,
maybe that's not our fault.
너희의 자격지심이지
Maybe that's just how you feel.
Now you're telling us how we feel.
자격지심이라고?
돈 얘긴 하는 게 아니었어
We never should have talked about this.
난 콘서트에 안 갈래
영 안 땡기거든
I'm gonna pass on the concert.
I'm just not in a very
"Hootie" place right now.
- 나도 안 가!
- 나도
-Me neither.
-Me too.
이왕 표는 산 거잖아
Guys, we bought the tickets.
너희들 그 큰 머리의
여유 공간을 위해 쓰라고
Then you'll have extra seats
for all your tiaras and stuff.
왜 날 쳐다봐?
Why did you look at me
when you said that?
우리도 가지 말자
So I guess now we can't go.
너희들끼리 가면 되잖아
꼭 몰려다녀야 해?
Do what you want. Do we always
have to do everything together?
참, 그거 말 되네
You know what? You're right.
Fine.
그래!
좋아!
나도!
알았어!
좋아!
그래!
All right.
우리끼리 갈 거야!
We're gonna go.
It's not for another six hours.
We're gonna go then.
아직 6시간 남았으니
그 때 갈 거야
챈들러?
- 응?
- 엄마!
- 준비됐어?
- 그럼
Are you ready?
Just let me grab my jacket
and tell you I had sex today.
재킷 가져올게
참, 나 오늘 섹스 했어
잠깐만!
What? You had sex today?
오늘 섹스를 했다고?
다른 사람이 그렇게
말하니까 더 짜릿하네
It sounds even cooler
when somebody else says it!
나 끝내줬어
I was awesome. She was biting her lip
to stop from screaming.
여자가 신음소리 안 내려고
입술을 꽉 깨물었다니까
I know it's been a while,
but I took that as a good sign.
계속 그러기만 했지만
좋다는 증거 같았어
Still doing the screening?
지금도 전화 골라 받아?
난 오늘 섹스를 했어
I had sex today.
I never have to
answer that phone again.
저 전화를 안 받아도
상관없다고
'어떻게 하는지 알죠?'
At the sound of the beep,
you know what to do.
밥, 제이드예요
Hey, Bob. It's Jade.
당신이 날 바람맞혀서
정말 실망했어요
I wanted to tell you I was really hurt
when you didn 't show up yesterday.
And just so you know,
I ended up meeting a guy.
당신 기다리다가
어떤 남자를 만났는데...
- 나 밥이야
- 안녕
Bob here.
So you met someone, huh?
- 남자를 만났다고?
-그래요!
Yes, I did.
사실 두 시간 전에
그와 섹스를 했어요
In fact, I had sex
with him two hours ago.
어땠어?
So how was he?
잉!
'잉'이라니?
Oh, Bob, he was nothing
compared to you.
그 남잔 자기하곤
비교도 안 돼요
자기 이름을 외칠까 봐
입술을 깨물 정도였어
I bit my lip to keep from
screaming your name.
이거 기분 좋은걸?
Well, that makes me feel so good.
방법을 모르는지
흔들어대기만 했어요
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
자기가 경험하지 못한
새로운 테크닉이겠지
Maybe he had some kind of new style
that you're not familiar with.
익숙해지면 나아질 거야
You have to get used to it.
익숙해질 틈도 없이
끝내 버리던걸 뭐
There wasn 't much time
to get used to it...
...if you know what I mean.
나 콘서트를 즐길
기분이 아냐
You know what? I'm not gonna
be able to enjoy this.
내 생일인데 모두가 함께
왔어야 했다고
I know. It's my birthday.
We all should be here.
So let's go.
그냥 가자
딱 한 곡만 듣고 가자
Well, maybe we should stay
for one song.
It would be rude to them
for us to leave now.
그냥 나가 버리면
예의가 아니잖아
자기들끼리 재미있게
놀고 있을 거야
The guys are probably
having a great time.
한 번만 더 하자고
Come on, you guys.
One more time.
좋아
- 하나
- 아냐!
One.
- 정말 멋졌어!
- 죽여줬어!
-Amazing!
-Excellent!
I can't believe the guys missed it!
딴 얘들도 봤어야 했는데
딴 얘들이라니?
참!
What guys?
Oh, yeah.
실례해요
모니카 겔러 맞죠?
Excuse me.
Aren't you Monica Geller?
-Do I know you?
-You were my baby-sitter!
- 누구시죠?
- 내 베이비시터였잖아요
Oh, my God!
Little Stevie Fisher?
세상에, 스티비 피셔?
잘지냈니?
How have you been?
그럼요
저 변호사 됐어요
Good. I'm a lawyer now.
8살 짜리가
변호사는 무슨?
You can't be a lawyer.
You're 8.
만나서 반가웠어요
무대 뒤에 가 봐야 해서
It was nice to see you.
I gotta run backstage.
- 무대 뒤에?
- 밴드가 저희 고객이거든요
Wait, backstage?
My firm represents the band.
- 로스예요
- 챈들러요
밴드 만나 보러 갈래요?
You guys wanna meet the group?
- 좋죠!
- 그럼요!
가요
Come on.
혹시 우리 아버지와
놀아났었어요?
Are you one of the ones
that fooled around with my Dad?
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 생일 축하해
Hey, you guys!
Happy birthday!
고마워
Oh, thank you.
어젯밤에 어땠어?
How was your night last night?
지겨웠지 뭐
너희들은?
Oh, well, it pretty much sucked.
How was yours?
Ours pretty much sucked too.
우리도 재미없었어
참, 스티비 피셔를 만났어
기억나?
But I ran into Stevie Fisher.
Remember him?
그럼, 내가 돌봐 줬었는데
아버지는 잘 계신대?
Oh, yeah!
I used to baby-sit him.
Hey, how's his dad?
그런가 봐
Good.
그것만 제외한다면
끔찍한 밤이었어
Aside from that, the evening
was pretty much a bust.
Yeah, we really missed you guys.
너희들도 보고 싶었고
우리도 생각해 봤는데
정말 한심한 것 같아
Yeah, we were just saying,
this whole thing is so stupid.
돈 문제로 우리들이
다툰다는 것이...
We just have to really, really
not let stuff like money, get like
Is that a hickey?
그거 키스 자국이야?
아냐, 엎어져서 그래
Oh, no, I just....
I fell down.
남자 입술에?
On someone's lips?
누가 그런 거야?
Where'd you get the hickey?
그냥, 파티에 갔다가...
You know, a party or
What party?
무슨 파티?
파티는 무슨
그냥 사람들 모임이었지
It wasn't a party
so much as a...
...a gathering of people.
음식, 음악에...
밴드도 있었고
With food and music and...
...and the band.
'후티와 블로우피쉬'하고
파티에 갔어?
You partied with
Hootie and the Blowfish?
Yes. Apparently, Stevie and Hootie
are like this.
그래, 스티비하고 후티가
이런 사이더라고
Who gave you that hickey?
그 자국은 누가 남겼어?
That would be the work of a Blowfish.
블로우피쉬 작품이야
어쩜 이럴 수가!
I can't believe it!
I can't believe this!
우린 집에서 조이의
손가락만 구경했는데
We're just sitting at home,
trying to guess Joey's fingers...
너희들은 블로우피쉬와
파티를 하면서
...and you're partying
and having fun and all:
목까지 헌납했어?
"Hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck!"
우리 탓하지 마
너희들이 안 갔잖아
Don't blame us.
You could've been there.
가난한 친구들
세상구경 시켜 주려고?
What? As part of your
"poor friends outreach program"?
직장이네
Oh, great. It's work.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry we make more than you.
우리가 너희들보다
많이 벌기는 하지만
죄책감 가질 순 없잖아
우린 열심히 일한다고
But we're not gonna feel guilty.
We work really hard.
누구는 빈둥대고?
And we don't work hard?
모니카예요
호출이 와서요
It's Monica. I got a page.
돈이 좀 들더라도
하고 싶은 것이 있잖아
It's just that sometimes we like
to do stuff that costs a little more.
And you feel like we hold you back.
- 우리가 방해가 돼?
-그래!
아냐!
리온, 잠시만요
Leon, wait.
얘들아!
Guys!
I don't understand.
이해를 못하겠어요
The steaks were a gift
from the meat vendor.
정육업자가 준 선물이지
뇌물이 아니에요
That was not a kickback.
I'll just replace them,
and we can forget the whole thing.
그게 문제가 된다면
돌려 보낼게요
회사 방침이라뇨?
What corporate policy?
알았어요
나 해고됐어
I just got fired.
여기 계산서요
4달러 12센트예요
Here's your check. That'll be $4. 1 2.
내가 낼게
Let me get that.
You got 5 bucks?
5달러만 빌려 줄래?
Here comes the beep.
You know what to do.
'삐 소리가 들리면
어떻게 하는지 알죠?'
나예요
Hi, it's me.
Listen, Bob.
I'm probably way out of line here.
밥, 도저히 못 참겠어요
벌써 3년이나 흘렀고
애인도 있겠지만
It's been three years, and you 're
probably seeing someone else now...
...but if we could have one night
together, for old time 's sake....
단 하룻밤만 함께 지내요
옛 정을 생각해서
강렬하고 화끈한 밤을
다시 한 번만...
One hot, steamy, wild night....